{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_House_of_Representatives_elections_in_California,_1880",
    "predicate": "property/votes",
    "object": "172",
    "human_readable": "The United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880 received 172 votes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9769449234008789,
            "question": "What was the number of votes received in the United States House of Representatives elections in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9332592487335205,
            "question": "Who won the elections for the United States House of Representatives in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8658047318458557,
            "question": "Were there any notable events related to the elections for the United States House of Representatives in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8009760975837708,
            "question": "Were there other elections besides those for the United States House of Representatives held in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7596453428268433,
            "question": "How did public opinion influence the outcomes of the elections for the United States House of Representatives in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6616144180297852,
            "question": "When did the United States House of Representatives elections take place in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.615994930267334,
            "question": "What political parties were represented in the elections for the United States House of Representatives in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4433533847332001,
            "question": "In which state were the elections for the United States House of Representatives held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4238646626472473,
            "question": "What year did the elections for the United States House of Representatives occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38876670598983765,
            "question": "How many votes were needed to win a seat in the United States House of Representatives during that election?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880 received 172 votes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1436_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did the elections for the United States House of Representatives occur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1436_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which state were the elections for the United States House of Representatives held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1436_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political parties were represented in the elections for the United States House of Representatives in California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1436_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1436_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text does not mention the number of votes received by The United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not mention anything about the number of votes received by the United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about the number of votes received by the California district during the 1880 United States House of Representatives elections. The documents discuss various aspects of the election, such as when it was held, how many seats were up for election, and some issues that dominated the year's elections, but do not include specific vote counts for any particular state or district."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}